good morning scobie's good morning good
morning first I'd like to show off some
hardware that I just purchased in the
comic AMA space
this is inferior to one you'll buy
because it's a crappy one here's a brand
new Toyota giraffe I know we're it
afford right now and then we have a
lovely one second I don't think that's
how you do that no I think it goes the
other way you just hold over now 60
years 60 people this early yeah 64 high
so there's a cow power I just bought it
at the comedy shop
I'm just gonna plug it in down here to
my convenient OBD port of it oh wait
shit no we can't do this oh we didn't
think this through at all what oh that's
terrible
cuz now we don't have any kin how does
anyone overdue there's only one OBD port
oh we didn't think this through at all
I'll never have to go get the wire again
maybe the wire inside I put the water
inside oh that's the tragedy we didn't
think that through no no we really
didn't think that through we can't use a
Toyota giraffe and a Ford because the
collar power isn't gonna transmit the
cans now why did I think that would work
I thought that was to OVD Vegas well
there's an obd on the power which will
give the pan of power to be fair we'd
have power we wouldn't have camp do we
one can we walk in alright because
otherwise what are we taking the Ford
for so we go to the racetrack today guys
in preparing for self racing cars so
what up with that creep into them but
this is this is what
oh my God we're like clowns where is
this shit is it now show them our
beautiful antenna map for 114 viewers
wait we have 140 people watching us be
idiots yeah Oh No inside we have to go
with the wire I think anyway okay
alright let's go inside let's go back
inside
oh there's the wire no wait there's the
wire oh this way oh why is down there
found the wire
okay well that's half the battle I'm I
don't really don't think I left the
great pan inside I mean maybe I did it's
a little bit annoying
unfortunately this USB wire is just
slightly ever so too short um also if we
lost that great Panda we don't have too
many of those yeah that was my test we
can't just go to the cafe I shop and
Biograph a McHenry no no okay so that's
just gonna kind of snake down there just
loop that like that we got a white panda
we had a white panda I put it inside
really is why is it called a gray panda
that's great oh I was sitting on it guys
alright so let's plug in our USB wire to
our gray panda here check it out
there we go nice grape and equality this
is a high quality great pan you know we
put the crappy ones in our other cars
put all like the demo units in our other
cars all right we'll snake the antenna
wire down here good thing the antenna
wire is long
ah well I don't know well we got a lot
of scope is this point I was expecting
like 30 people probably dropping off
this is terrible
you've got 90 now Oh 90 people watching
this content yeah yes it does have GPS
great pandas GPS look I'm screwed in the
GPS right now well so that was just
total whale a sitting on there no no no
no like we're gonna get the giraffe in
the column of power none of that shit's
gonna work this is a Ford we need a
forger F you know in the Ford Fusion we
won't tell the scope he's about the Ford
Fusion tragedy can you guys stop the
race later oh well so we go to the race
this weekend or go to self racing cars
um but today konna a I rented out a
track we rented out an airfield and
we're gonna go test our high-speed Prius
um so Ricardo's already on the way there
and now Harold and I are gonna drive
down and we're gonna test it so there's
an amount someone said George is out of
breath setting all this up I know
wouldn't it be great if you know the
thing could now tell us if we set up the
Greg hander properly Wow our front of
turn usable shit all right cool that's
that's paired oh look at look at how
nice that is with the uh with the fact
that it goes like that
oh yeah sure reboot it so we don't
because that's the old branch these
things are supposed to reboot on update
I don't know if that actually works
somebody asked about the woman that got
killed by the uber car we don't talk
about that investigation with nobody I
will say this about the woman who got
killed by the uber car nobody has all
the facts yet when the investigation
comes out
be very interesting to read and discuss
but right now it's all just speculation
yeah runway tends to be straight good
for ping-pong Prius fix Oh ping-pong is
that what we're doing today wait okay so
can I Drive why is it blinking is that
good that sounds good there we go
Coolidge or it just start press oh the
door is ajar wait I don't have power
steering passenger door enjoy my do it
oh you are right just start press brake
this cars too
oh hey gotta put it in park then press
Gregg okay now we're ready to drive no
difficult up what the hell is that merch
in our branch
oh this probably isn't the latest code
real it's not a lot of update anymore
they do should we get the laptop I guess
so let's all vision D oh I call it works
Wow yeah full screen timeline I don't
know what that means full screen
timeline bro have you heard that's so
good I don't really know where we're
going I'm just gonna go to 280 cuz I
don't want to go the other way
well we're definitely not going to the
Bay Bridge I think that's the fastest
way no no I don't Joe I don't take the
Bay Bridge in the morning you want to go
through San Jose yeah which can't be
hundred miles longer that doesn't make
sense
sorry an hour long now but I'm no way
I'm going to Bay Bridge this morning
oh it's laggy and you're probably on 40
oh I think it's just shitty here yeah
what are they cold look we have a lot of
Skokie's because they're the mapping one
yesterday was exciting and now they're
like it's just like I should talking in
a car but doesn't even sell drive this
Ford does not sell Drive I'm driving the
Ford just so when I crash we know whose
fault it is
oh my god oh my god alright that was
overly stressful is it what are we going
to the races
what is he cold oh I don't know don't
like people know those kind of things
so this is running Schafer plus we're
driving a shipper plus car we are
driving is really hard you guys like
that you're driving much easier oh you
definitely need to take the Bay Bridge
no it's two hours and no traffic
wait first off it's two hours fuck that
second off really I have to take the Bay
Bridge yeah I mean it said it was two
and a half hours from where Ricardo
lives so it's much better this way
it's furthermore Ricardo though yeah cuz
you can't cross the mountain you need to
go all the way all the mouth okay well
how do I get to the Bay Bridge from here
wait why don't we just use our improved
ways experience and yeah let's do that
sorry woman yeah dress frozen landing
Crows Landing rose Landing Road in
Modesto fits of yes done let's go
let's get started drive safely yes wait
turn right father if you turn right well
I don't know if your orientation
libraries working is that right all
right I probably think they're going the
other I think it thinks I'm going the
other way this is my orientation with
his new boxes
what who wrote this shit
things are going that way are you
stationary
I wasn't stationary when it got the fix
it should know that so this is the wrong
way let's help follow this road go
straight oh good we go good we don't
have the crappy yard we got the high
quality phone there better need all
these wires it's like got a broken
screen though no GPS this ball can tell
you which direction you're going might
turn on I suppose but we were already
driving the great panda should have way
got in to fix I honestly think that's a
bug in the orientation library honestly
no you know what maybe ways computes its
own orientation this might be a way ease
interface issue that's true because I
probably don't want to rely on you know
oh now it knows there we go I think ways
I think ways did it man yeah man we knew
all about look at that high quality
grape and a shot so oh that's nice where
we are the actual location all right so
I want to turn on Ocean Avenue stay to
the left
there should be towns where they name
every street after emo songs
yeah let's blame ways exactly please you
guys totally ways we started ways late
it probably computes its own orientation
which can you really blame ways for that
miles turn left to I to eighteen or in
one point twelve miles in fact how many
people are watching this show when it's
64 now alright good they're all drop
this terrible this is tax is a worse
this is a horoscope you really don't
have anything planned for you guys we're
just driving two hours to a racetrack in
a non self-driving car but it is oh
that's true which can are you going to
race the Prius well okay so we're gonna
know Ricard is gonna repair to go to
Walmart to buy cones this morning we'll
set up a drag strip who wins a Prius
hybrid or a Ford Fusion Hybrid let's go
let's find out
I'm sure II periscope that no it's too
exciting we're definitely gonna drag
racer cars if we periscope anything it
needs to be that if we're paying $600 to
run out of track we're definitely drag
racing our cars I'm excited for the
jacket we were gonna bring the Acura but
you guys know that's my least favorite
car oh my god they're small children up
ahead
somebody asked about Kira I don't know
what that is Oh Kira water back here I
don't know something about why you
committed that to github or something oh
I took it back I just put it back on Geo
hot no no the other guys didn't didn't
contribute anything to it so I took it
back all right so now this starts the
little pile of comma hardware we have in
every car look at how smooth that weighs
this Google Maps that just seems hard
$600 for an hour no no no no no the day
we get the whole track for the day we're
any other an airstrip I don't know you
probably didn't have to do it but
whatever now we'll have a track George
do you use Ida Pro for all the time
do you like item that's right I mean
here's the thing how many people try to
like oh I'm gonna make something better
than I died and then you don't you just
use Ida that's always an absence but we
are gonna make something better than a
plan X oh my god Waze is better than
Google Maps I don't know about that is
it I'm convinced that ways sometimes
takes you stupid ways because you're
like a baby way there I mean it's kinda
like a we're gonna take people to Taco
Bell if you don't bike on a I premium is
this a play I know here all right
driving in San Francisco is super
stressful
I'm a Muni should we stop and pick these
people up bye people
any progress on fusion giraffe interface
oh well you saw that you see all the
progress right look at that blinker look
at that that just makes it hard for your
she learning to classify right there Joe
how do you guys like the HDR chto nice
what do I do with my becoming what are
you doing your VidCon I don't know if I
was about to be worthless did you clean
this thing someone asks don't talk to
you about this Decker don't talk to me
about the sticker are you guys using
Sprint t-mobile yeah we got t-mobile oh
no that's my phone I ain't a they
looking really likes HDR yeah virtually
Chris says his is blurry when it's
focused that's amazing no I fixed add
new folks come in yesterday dude did you
test the new one is it still blurry know
if it's still blurry in the new one I
don't know what you did I worked really
hard on that I spent like an hour I
retuned the loop he says still blurry no
oh no you didn't pull right no it can't
be still far it's impossible I removed
the blurry
no send me around I'll take a look at it
I you really don't know how it could
still be blurry I wrote the best
autofocus ever to admin zero my keys to
admin keys program
what's an admin key does somebody have
rude on my car that isn't me
now to your Anna Ford talk about Ford
problems oh no we're in a four talking
about Ford problems actually we took
this car because the actor Sox it's not
driving at all and I just AM making a
wrong turn because that's not right if
only the car if only that was augmented
reality in a heavy traffic oh my god how
far did you think it was it said three
hours yesterday I was already confused
why you oh my god why am I gonna this
guy's I don't know why I ever agree to
do things I usually regret it will old
grape and drives get one two maps all
only good ones
if you're grape n is blurry you saw
yesterday you saw yesterday about how
many so we tried three drives and one of
them was good enough for maps but maps
are super cool where's this bundle
that's a little gear probably oh and
what is that energy drink I don't know
that's the orange exuberance curve
amante
let's see if we can pair this to the car
while we're driving
oh no way we can't cuz we can't press
the Settings button you okay
why not being able to press the Settings
button yeah like our products och I
don't know why anyone bought them I'm
very upset about that
yeah okay no no I've complained about
that a lot if you're not racing a GTR
then you should not race well what I'm
racing a Ford Fusion Platinum Hybrid
that's right
what's the ETM a new model well how
about this let's change the let's try to
use the intelligent features of this car
adaptive speed cruise to low to activate
we go now oh yeah we're going
oh yeah we're in adaptive cruise mode
alright the Ford is driving the Ford is
driving well kind of I don't see if it's
gonna stop for this car oh my god I
don't really really does it see the car
now or is it going to try to accelerate
into them
you should give extra points for mapping
new roads
I got accelerate here and not use the
Ford driving because I want to make that
light alright let's go
get ready for heavy traffic yep
okay the word is driving but just didn't
see that car at all if people think our
fusions bad okay let's see if the lane
keep is gonna work that's what I'm
really excited about Blaine keep I paid
$1,000 for this option I really did oh
my god oh god boat America I gotta help
America American economy this is the
number ship Shh
I'll buy whoever makes a better car
aside from porting cars what projects do
you want people to contribute to well
whoever works at Ford could contribute
to making this less shitty wait why
doesn't it see the lanes I don't
understand camera out up there hope I
didn't cover the lens
this is supposed to see the lanes
oh maybe have to engage no no it's
already engaged this is a Ford stop and
go though it's really not that terrible
it's quite smooth yeah not that terrible
doesn't think there's not a girl
yeah is Lane keeping his malicious no no
no it doesn't see the lanes for some
reason they were dropping viewers 48 I
believe the scope is here so you can
listen to music oh my god
okay okay okay that was terrible you're
watching the car why'd you do that it's
like I'm gonna accelerate and then hit
the brakes activates above 40 miles an
hour oh that's why it doesn't work
should we at least wait till we get to
40 miles an hour that's not gonna happen
anytime soon
oh my god why did I agree to go this way
we gotta cut out we gotta cut out oh it
did it good God Timothy viewers take
something up
hmm take off my logo Punk maverick buddy
what um oh my god
I was at the train station and this girl
whispered to the stomach turned around
what I just looked at that in the I'm
like yeah you didn't lo guy she's
mortified oh that's good
I only liked him we was controversial
now he's like trying to like rebrand
himself is like whatever I don't care
but you know oh by the dip that's right
by the I supported Logan Paul when he
was down by the dip all right I don't
even think we're gonna get to see Ford's
uh yeah this isn't gonna happen
but the stop it go is is not terrible
it's quite smooth it's good actually
yeah like this is quite usable when's
the next rap song we're waiting yo you
guys I wrapped my wrath let's go peace
unity to growing again all right people
do want to sit in traffic with us
but I need to probably like confirm that
we're going to the right place the right
place waze's got us oh you sure I'm sure
Waze is goddess brow it sounds about
right though doesn't it Modesto that's
what we're going no we're definitely
going alike like Cesar Chavez wrote or
whatever it is okay that's good yeah
we're good
your flow is surprisingly good thank you
I'm working on my flowers about your
wrap
I gotta be a better rapper all right we
gotta cut out here it's like overly
oh we were gonna run a Tesla this
morning but all right let's put them on
blast get a riff on socks their customer
service people don't talk to anybody I
get on the phone with don't lie can I
speak to a supervisor they're like okay
please hold I please hold it for 30
minutes and then they're like there's no
supervisors available but now what can I
do you think that's forgivable okay
maybe there really are two supervisors
available I call back an hour later they
do the same thing to me they don't just
tell me there's no supervisor better
like please hold
I think they just want you to hang up um
no you guys know it on the Facebook and
this doesn't work because get around oh
yeah and then they won't tell you why
they rejected your application and it's
because I don't have any friends on
Facebook because I don't have a Facebook
I have one Facebook that I used to sign
up for Jase wipe so doesn't we're in
cars the people under 30 that's the
problem like nice cars
yeah you can't rent a Tesla antero if
you're under so me that owns a fusion
says you need to set it to keep an aide
or something okay yeah hang on we can do
this let's try it oh it has various
levels alert eight and alert an aide and
you should put it to alert an aide okay
let's add it to alert innate how do I do
this this button this button oh here I
got you go driver
alert all this on available where is it
unavailable of eighty-eight percent
energy returned or unavailable driver
alert unavailable on involution that
picture it has a little picture of a
steering wheel and a cup of coffee and
it's unavailable I don't know if
anyone's ever complained about the Aeon
UI but uh sit intensity too high I think
I've already done this but I don't know
why it's unavailable right now
unavailable very tutorial without that
low arts a tutorial oh my god why is
this thing letting me do this
shouldn't I keep my eyes on the road
okay I can't do that one cuz I gotta
keep my eyes on the road but I can
certainly do the tutorials of all
traffic no honestly like our UI isn't
even bad compared to the Ford one it
says go to settings and it sounds
incredibly complicated a where I mean oh
settings oh I found it Oh driver's test
Oh boom boom lanky be says system mode
alert and aid we're good on that I'd
stop doing regen when I did that
intensity high good very good
cool good Brad alright David oh my God
we're never gonna get up to go fast what
was it doing it no shit
we're never gonna go fast enough thanks
David do they say this control no no you
can't be CEO and know how to code I know
about business I know about business
development I know how to make
partnership deals with large companies
those fuckers
so there's some kind of channel now who
claims that there's a way to do this so
if it turns out that I'm just an idiot
then I'm just an idiot but as far as I
can tell you can't actually run your own
programs on Qualcomm's DSP if you want
to run programs on Qualcomm DSP you have
to work with the OEM to get your thing
signed for production
now this isn't done for security this
isn't done for quality this is just
literally done to make some apps
shittier than others so basically it's
like you want your app to be not shitty
well you can pay the qualcomm money I
know but that's really what it is right
that's called digital protectionism
it's called rent-seeking and that's what
we are fighting against in addition to
nature okay so are we gonna go fast go
fast for it trying the stabilizer again
it's right yeah you have to press the on
button oh okay
I don't know it's actually kind of
confusing but sometimes press the on
button like it doesn't work I'm trying
to stay oh no no no no you got to press
the button it says button or something
there we go it's mites are blinking
oh that's improvement I don't know the
thing is hard to use I get it wrong all
the time stabilizer was working nice
last night huh yeah it was so stable
last night can we go to North 280 even
though it doesn't take us where we want
to go there's less traffic there that's
probably cuz nobody wants to go there
they just make all the roads go where
people want to go I know how this works
guys I'm sorry low battery can't be low
battery that's a lie
a little battery going back to manual
stabilization we brought that thing and
doesn't even work and I'll charge me the
micro USB to charge we're gonna add our
charger I am oh can we connect it to the
fort maybe it'll show up as a afford
connect to my guest so he keeps asking
if you like rice if I like rice did I
love rice like rice what race will be
going to well we're going to test track
mountain itself racing cars this weekend
self racing cars is this weekend um we
would periscope but I'm not gonna be
there because I'm going to a wedding I'm
going to flying to New York tomorrow
guys oh yeah no we're gonna race and we
should do well it's taking forever
two hours oh oh this is an hour 33 I
like ways yeah but is it correct says
we'll be there 1029 so reasonable and
that's even with waiting 50 minutes in
Bay Area Bridge traffic wait it doesn't
that doesn't add up the worst people are
such idiots on the bridge you know what
I wish I had right now the Civic the
Civic just drives all of this
I took the Civic to Oakland once what
the scope is like I did nothing I can't
do the wheel look at this look at this
non self-driving car correct it look at
this
how many interventions it requires this
is a level zero car six pretty close
okay fine
I've been on Mount because the locals
agents were okay that's true the grape
and up
what's your favorite car now George um
aside from a few incidents that we're
not going to talk about I like diffusion
this is nice this is like it's just it's
a nice car Ford has really stepped up
their game I mean okay everything about
like the electronics are shit but the
interior is is nice thirty it feels fast
[Music]
cars just really don't see you at all
and then like yeah you got to be quick
or you're gonna get hit survival of the
fittest
honestly you know Google is evil right
like I trust someone who says don't be
evil
I don't trust someone who says be good I
still trust them they're evil no no
Google's been nice to me over the years
I should really say that Facebook was
nice to me too but I'm kind if they got
me to use their product which
and not not even because of any new
political revelations just delete your
Facebook you should have deleted it
months ago years ago did you turn el
cast on on the stick someone else I did
turn our cast on on the stick so I can
see the ladies go away and now the
ladies are back I think it's just that
we're not going fast enough
I don't know why this car won't Lane
keep at low speeds okay somebody says 40
miles in the cutoff hey you want to get
the laptop out and have like a hackathon
while we drive and see if by the time we
get there we can get the foot or if that
means I'm gonna be doing that we could
switch no I can't look at a car you get
sick yeah I mankind look it's grandpa
like I have to spend at least half the
time looking outside but maybe if I'm in
an ultra-smooth for fusion platinum
hybrid oh you were just gonna cook
pecans pick them up no but like
seriously that's how far we made it in
an hour but then she's gonna waste her
tea - no no no we kick fib up we go back
to the lump it oh I see put this gonna
give it yeah I tried that but it's not
the gimbals I had a bad show me get
bolts out of batteries resistible try
the bottle I press this button what is
it now few light sounds bad
doesn't sound very stabilizing that
sounds bad it wasn't doing this doesn't
seem right but it look at say it looks
stable oh that's good to put the phone
in there that's destabilizing yeah well
we should have put it in a special
stabilizing case I came with this
ridiculous looking like mandolin case
wait there's a stabilizing knob on the
fact I have the same
okay discard us blind spot awareness
system but apparently even the data
speak it can only get what I understand
oh really I think so what does an op-amp
know so you can put the orientation
electronic oh we're gonna go fast now
for Leakey whoo yes it sees the lanes
oh yes go fast okay it's gonna lankey
let's say very okay we're allegedly
going if the lanes are detected now
everything is is it way keeping I can't
tell Oh
who wrote that autofocus did it
stabilized okay well this Lane keep
isn't working very well either
okay David is warning us that it will
definitely ping-pong Wow
why doesn't the ceilings unusable
but it's doing this it turns out
actually it's not that argument you've
got like you don't have to do that much
like I'm not touching anything right now
it's kind of driving but it's not
actually putting any torque in the wheel
which is going straight yeah it's
horrible these new evil 22 steering
wheel Platts 3d scanner and on the we
are I always thought that all these
systems except Tesla's but no torque of
the wheel and then Tesla it's a
horrifying amount of torque on the wheel
I'll figure out the stabilizer after
this
up to 42 viewers who I have to get over
here that's still a lot oh my god okay
why would I step on the gas does oh it
doesn't cancel on gas
now maybe not dangerous to be used what
did the huts mean impersonal the hearts
and means they like what we're doing I
don't know though I've never actually
use periscope as a user there's also
many different colors of Hearts kuia
whoppers yeah I'm really like Wendy's
makes like jr. bacon cheeseburgers I
don't think it's the same thing as a
whopper but like I couldn't tell you
what Wendy's is walk for us doesn't mean
we need have square burgers I think so
yeah why don't you stream on Instagram
it's the stream does this a Facebook I
do i do have an instagram you guys if
you look around you could find that now
I kick off people usually who I don't
actually know from it goodnight oh we're
gonna go fast okay all right let's try
at least one attempt at lane-keeping go
slow I'll go faster my fourth
who's that oh my god it just it just
forward collision warning thank God it
didn't ATP forward collision warning wow
this sucks
okay let's see if it's gonna okay thank
you blankie blankie blankie doing it
putting any torque on the wheel baby
doesn't seem to be moving much well here
we got a turn I think it might be doing
this okay guys that's the scope for
today make sure to hit that like and
subscribe button always check out the
shop coming guys slash shop buy things
they're good for you
that's it let's all we have to say maybe
we'll scope it the drag race between a
Ford Fusion Hybrid on a Prius hybrid who
will win take bets now everyone's
already found the fuse gambling not
legal in all jurisdictions please check
your local laws always comply with
regulations yeah merica right this is
the great shout out of American versus
Japanese hybrid muscle alright my bass
goes
now you push down and you can stop
broadcast